<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Erik Sapir</title><link>https://esapir.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Erik Sapir</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://esapir.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Let’s Reverse Engineer Wilco</title><link>https://esapir.github.io/posts/lets-reverse-engineer-wilco/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esapir.github.io/posts/lets-reverse-engineer-wilco/</guid><description>If you are a software engineer, it’s likely that you’ve already been asked to reverse-engineer someone else’s feature. Was it someone from Product, who came to you and asked to build a feature “that works exactly, but exactly, like in this other app?” Or did the request come from Marketing? In any case, it happens all the time and makes perfect sense. Given limited resources, it’s usually better to spend them on innovation rather than on trying to reinvent the wheel.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://esapir.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esapir.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Menca comes with a built-in contact form, that you can use with Formspree service to handle up to 50 submissions per month for free. You could also easily switch to another contact form service if you want.</description></item><item><title>Elements</title><link>https://esapir.github.io/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esapir.github.io/elements/</guid><description>A paragraph looks like this — Globally incubate standards compliant channels before scalable benefits. Quickly disseminate superior deliverables whereas web-enabled applications. Quickly drive clicks-and-mortar catalysts for change before vertical architectures. Credibly reintermediate backend ideas for cross-platform models. Continually reintermediate integrated processes through technically sound intellectual capital. Holistically foster superior methodologies.
Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description></item><item><title>Who am I?</title><link>https://esapir.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esapir.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Erik, and for over 18 years, I have been designing and implementing innovative solutions to challenging problems. Throughout my career, I have held several technical leadership positions, including eight years of leading the R&amp;amp;D department at uMake, an award-winning 3D design app. Presently, I am working at Wilco, where I have the opportunity to help software engineers all around the globe enhance their technical skills and become better professionals.</description></item></channel></rss>